Mai Hung Vu

Deer Park, Victoria 3023 M: 0401 070 232

Hung.vm2574@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mai-hung-vu-565b1bb2/

https://github.com/herohung093

Career Objective

Talented and experienced Software Engineer in web and mobile application development, enterprise software and development cycle optimization. With a can-do attitude and enthusiasm towards learning new technologies, I'm able to carry out challenging technical tasks. Through University and side projects, I have developed the ability to learn new concepts and technologies quickly and be able to apply those on projects.

Key Skills Summary

Programing languages: Intermediate: Java, Kotlin, JavaScript.

Basic: Python, C++, Scala, C#.

Operating systems: Intermediate: Windows Server, Centos.

Backend: Intermediate: Spring (MVP, Security), Spring Boot. Relational

Databases, SQL and ORM technologies (JPA2, Hibernate), RESTful

APIs.

Frontend: Intermediate: Android(MVP, MVVM, Dagger 2, RxJava), Web

Services.

Basic: React.JS.

Methodologies: Agile (Jira), SDLC.

Education

Professional Year Program

Feb 2019 - Present

Performance Education, Melbourne

Key Subjects: Australian Business Culture, Environment and Workplace Skills, Professional Business Communication.

Master Spring & Hibernate

April 2018 - Oct 2018

Udemy, Melbourne

Bachelor of Information Technology

Mar 2016 - Dec 2018

La Trobe University, Melbourne, Australia

Achievements – Course WAM 80. Recognized as top 15% of high achievement students worldwide by The Golden Key Club.

Academic Projects

Corporate insights App

Aug 2018 - Sep 2018

La Trobe University, Melbourne

This project focus was to enable current and prospective investors to make the most of the eXtensible Business Reporting Language (XBRL) data submitted to

Mai Hung Vu

Objective:

regulators, in real time. The application was to pull the most current information. calculate and visualize several useful and relevant ratios and indicators in a visually

easy to grasp way.

Spring boot for back-end server, PostgreSQL as a database. The application is Tools:

deployed on Heroku, the application is available on both IOS and Android. The

project you Agile as a project management methodology.

As part of a team of 4. I took part in designing, developing, testing application **Duties:**

architecture and user interface on android version. Besides, I also developed APIs on

the server side.

My team and I were selected to bring our product to the La Trobe University 26th Result:

Engineering, Data Science and Information Technology Showcase as our team won

the prize of outstanding implementation.

Kio App

La Trobe University, Melbourne

Objective:

To create a forecasting system for data analysis using fuzzy logic to predict electricity pricing in Queensland, based on historical data.

Tools:

Python was used as the programing language and data was saved in excel format. Matplotlib and NumPy to visualize and clean up data, Jupiter was used to produce report with coding format.

Duties:

- Remove outliers of the output variable from the datasets (both training and test), rebuild the training and the test datasets.
- Select appropriate values or fuzzy subsets for linguistic variables used in fuzzy rules.
- List the fuzzy rules that are generated by using statistical analysis (correlation coefficients) with heuristics; Implement fuzzy system, where all membership functions involved in the system should be plotted clearly.
- Report the system performance in terms of the average relative error for both training and testing datasets, analyze the effects of membership functions and defuzzification methods.

Results

Kio can achieve approximately 92% of precision and was selected to implement with real-time data flow.

Employment History

Android Developer

Feb 2018 - Nov 2018

Hixel, Melbourne

- Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Work with outside data sources and APIs.
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance.
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency.
- Work on Android model such as MVVM, MVP and libraries namely RxJava, Dagger 2, MPAndroid Chart.

Java Developer Nov 2018 - present

Dragon Dental Co Ltd, Vietnam

- Design, implement and maintain Java application phases.
- To take part in software and architectural development activities.
- Conduct software analysis, programming back-end application using Spring Boot, JDBC and Hibernate, testing and debugging.
- Transforming requirements into stipulations.
- Develop, test, implement and maintain application software.
- Recommend changes to improve established Java application processes.
- Develop technical designs for application development.

Personal Attributes

- Excellent in brainstorming and analyzing skills, as proved when I worked as mobile application developer (designing UI and apply technical skills to fulfill requirements).
- Great communication as I have 2 years' experience as a supervisor in hospitality industry.

Hobbies and Interest

Sport: Soccer and gym. Would love to go the gym after a long hard work or and enjoy a weekend soccer match with my team.

Movies: I'm a big fan of Peaky Blinders and Game of Thrones.

References

Dr. Torab Torabi

Department of Computer Science and Computer Engineering La Trobe University Bundoora, VIC. 3083

email: t.torabi.latrobe.edu.au

Phone: +61 3 9479-1057 Fax: +61 3 9479-3060

Mis. Tegan Sherwin

Director of Dragon Dental Co Ltd. Email: tegan.sherwin95@gmail.com.

Phone: 0467 251 995